

JOHN RAFAEL D. YAPCHIONGCO FLUTTER DEVELOPER

0921-315-8302 jr.yapchiongco@gmail.com 102 Zone 4 Sta. Lucia, Magarao, Camarines Sur

SUMMARY

As a passionate and versatile IT professional, I possess a strong academic foundation and diverse technical expertise across programming languages, frameworks, and software tools. As a quick learner and collaborative team player, I am driven to apply my diverse skills to create innovative technological solutions.

EXPERIENCE

Part Time - Social Media Manager, Uptown Coffee - Naga City

Nov 2024 - Present

- Developed and executed social media strategies across platforms, increasing brand engagement.
- Built and maintained a loyal online community by engaging with followers and responding to customer inquiries.
- Designed and produced high-quality promotional posters tailored for social media platforms.

Freelance - Academic Coach, Euler Ptolemy - Naga City

Dec 2020 - Present

- Providing academic support and guidance to students both from international schools and within the country.
- Collaborating with students to create and develop their work and projects.
- Leveraging subject matter expertise to assist students in completing their coursework and achieving academic success.

Internship - Wordpress Web Developer - The Umonics Method

Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

- Contributed to the development and maintenance of company WordPress websites.
- Participated in project management activities, such as progress tracking and team collaborations with other departments.
- Developed a working understanding of the WordPress ecosystem and its capabilities.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Jun 2019 - Jun 2024

Ateneo de Naga University

• Capstone Project Title: Developing a Mobile Proximity Pet Adoption App

Junior High School & Senior High School

Jun 2013 - March 2019

Ateneo de Naga University

• Strand: Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics (STEM)

ORGANIZATIONS

The Ateneo Consortium of Technological, Informational and

Computing Sciences (TACTICS)

Member Jun 2019 - Jun 2024

ADNU Golden Galiants

Vice President

Aug 2023 - Jun 2024

Audit Officer

Mar 2023 - Aug 2023

PROJECTS

Pawster Project Mobile Application

Jun 2022 - May 2023

Ateneo de Naga University

 A platform that revolves around pet adoption and rehoming where the digitalization of the adoption process allows the adopters to fully achieve adopting through a location-based mobile application.

ACHIEVEMENTS, HONORS & AWARDS

President's Lister

Second Semestral QPI: 3.7 **S/Y 2021 - 2022**

SKILLS

IT Support Web Development Project Management

Mobile Development UI / UX

IT SKILLSET & PROFICIENCIES

• Programming Languages: C++, Python, R, Java, Dart

• Database: Firebase NoSQL, Oracle MySQL

• Frameworks: Flutter, Ruby on Rails, Bootstrap, Django

• Software & Tools: Microsoft Office, WordPress, UI/UX(AdobeXD, Figma, Canva)

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux

CERTIFICATES

Google IT Support Specialization

CCNA: Switching, Routing and Wireless Essentials

Cisco Cybersecurity Essentials

· SAP Business One Basics

· Agile Project Management

GENERAL SKILLS

Problem Solving Skills	Organizational Skills	Digital Skills
Trouble Shooting	Critical Thinking	Data Analysis
Maintenance	Attention to Detail	

HOBBIES

Game Modding	Studying in Online Courses	Die-cast Car Collecting
Listening to Music	Playing Video Games	Reading Comics
Keyboard Modding	Watching Series	Cooking

LANGUAGES

English: ProficientTagalog: Native/FluentBicol: Native/Fluent